BRENDAN NUGARA

P (416) 738-8751 E bnugara@rogers.com L linkedin.com/in/brendan-nugara W

I am a Computer Science student at Queen's University, and I have been coding for over 5 years. In my studies, as well as on my own time, I have learned and had experience with data structures, algorithms, and the software development lifecycle. Outside of my academics, I aim to do projects with my peers, participate in hackathons and expand my knowledge in areas including cloud computing on platforms such as Azure, Google Cloud, and AWS.

EXPERIENCE

May 2020 - August 2020

Software Developer Intern • CogniFrame • Toronto, ON

Received training on web development with Angular and Spring Boot, as well as training on the fundamentals of machine learning and artificial intelligence.

May 2020 - August 2020

Data Analytics and Quality Assurance Intern • WeTraq • Toronto, ON

Analyzed data provided by New Relic APM to track and log abnormal occurrences to help improve WeTraq's mobile application, GuardIO. Tested android releases of GuardIO app for problems prior to launch.

May 2020 - Present

Chief Technology Officer • Muse Magazine • Kingston, ON

Manage the organization's WordPress website, as well as the development of the Muse Magazine mobile app.

September 2020 - Present

Teaching Assistant • Queen's School of Computing • Kingston, ON

Tasked with providing support to students and helping with marking for Discrete Mathematics for Computing I at Queen's University.

RECENT PROJECTS

Helpify • uses React and Google Firebase

A web application developed with my peers to allow people unable to go out during quarantine to reach out to members of their community by submitting a ticket for another member of the community to fulfill. My role was front-end developer, where I used React to build the user interface.

SPCA Website • uses PHP, SQL, HTML, CSS and JavaScript

A web application built to mimic the tasks carried out by the SPCA. It uses php to connect to a MySQL database to create, read, update, and delete data on animals, donors, and employees.

PROGRAMING LANGUAGES

github.com/BrendanNug

- C/C#/C++
- Java
- Python
- JavaScript
- SQL
- R
- PHP

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Computing (Honours)

Queen's University, Kingston, ON

3.83 GPA, Dean's Honour List

Expected Graduation – Spring 2022

CERTIFICATIONS/COURSES

Azure Fundamentals Certification Microsoft, February 2020

Alpha Student Ambassador Microsoft, August 2020

Data Structures and Algorithms Athabasca University, May 2020 -August 2020

INTERESTS

Swimming, Cars, Music, and Programming